jacetube.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy – JaceTube.Com

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

 **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

We do not collect information from visitors of our site.

or other details to help you with your experience.

 **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you or enter information on our site.

 **How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

 **How do we protect your information?**

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

We do not use an SSL certificate

 **•** We only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or private information like names, email addresses, or credit card numbers.

 **Do we use ‘cookies’?**

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

However, you will still be able to place orders .

 **Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Google**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.

 **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

 **CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

 **We collect your email address in order to:**

 **To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:**

 **  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at**

and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.

 **Disclaimer**

JaceTube.Com doesn’t host any content on its own server and just linking to or embedding content that was uploaded to popular Online Video hosting sites like DailyMotion, Youtube, Google Drive, Xtube, Xvideos, Pornhub, MyVidster, OpenloadMovies, Redtube and such sites. All trademarks, Videos, trade names, service marks, copyrighted work, logos referenced herein belong to their respective owners/companies. JaceTube.Com is not responsible for what other people upload to 3rd party sites. We urge all copyright owners, to recognize that the links contained within this site are located somewhere else on the web or video embedded are from other various site like included above! If you have any legal issues, please contact appropriate media file owners / hosters. If you have any legal issues, please contact the appropriate media file owners or host sites.

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

jacetube.com

Brgy San Antonio

Pasig City, NCR 1605

Philippines

jacegeronimo21@gmail.com

Last Edited on 2016-07-26
